Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Irish Americana Collection AIA.031.004
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Sheet Music (Irish), 1817-1995
  - K
    - Katy Darling's Farewell to Dermot, 1852 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Katy Mahone, 1894 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Keep the Horseshoe, 1880 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Kelly, I'm Glad to See You Back, 1919 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Kelly, the Carman, 1898 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Kellys Are At It Again, The, 1913 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Kelly's Gone to Kingdom Come, 1910 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Kelly's Masquerade Ball, 1892 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Kerry Dance, The, 1941 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Kerry Mills Barn Dance, 1908 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Kilcoy Schottische, The, undated (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Kilkenny, 1911, 1912 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Killaloe, undated (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Killaloo, 1915 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Killarney, [circa 1915] (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Killarney (2), nd, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Killarney Colleen, 1917 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Killarney Kate, 1924 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Killarney, My Home O'er the Sea, 1908, 1911 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Killarney, the Blarney, and You, 1924 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Killbarney Trip to Paris, The, undated (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Kind of a Girl I Mean, The, 1918 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - King Finnigan, 1901 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - King Mickey Malone, 1910 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Kitty, 1923 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Kitty Donohue, 1921 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Kitty Dooley, 1903 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Kitty O'Neil, 1904 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Kitty Tyrrell, undated (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - K-K-K-Katy, 1918 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Knights of St. Patrick, The, 1878 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Kosher Kitty Kelly, 1925 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - L
    - Laddie Buck, 1908 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Laddie Buck of Mine, 1920 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Lads Who Live in Ireland, The, 1864 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Lament of the Irish Emigrant, The, 1843 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Lament of the Irish Lover, 1847 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Land O'Romance, The, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Lannagin's Shillalah, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Larry Moore, 1890 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Lass from the County Mayo, The, 1913 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Lass I Love, The, 1900 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Lass of Limerick Town, The, 1917 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Lass that I Loved in Killarney, The, 1913 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Last Rose of Summer, The, 1925 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Last Sod of Turf, The, 1918 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Laughing Irish Eyes, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Learn to Smile ( from The O'Brien Girl ), 1921 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Leaves of the Shamrock, The, 1920 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Legacy, The ( Part III of Ireland ), undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Legend of the Maguire, The, 1904 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Leprehaun, The, 1935 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Let Me Glance At Dear Old Ireland Once Again, 1911 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Let the Farmer Praise His Grounds, 1916 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Let the Rest of the World Go By, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Let's Help the Irish Now, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Lights of Bantry Bay, The, 1911 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Limerick Girls, 1902 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Listen to that Irish Ragtime Band, 1912 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Little American Boy, 1943 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Little Annie Rooney, nd, 1890, 1925 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Little Colleen I Love, The, 1908 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Little Galway Cloak, The, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Little Homes of Ireland, The, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Little Irish Dance, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Little Irish Girl, The, 1903 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Little Irish Home, 1937 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Little Irish Rose, 1928 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Little Katie Dooley is My Wife Now, 1890 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Little Maggie Ann, 1879 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Little Maggie Brady, 1911 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Little Maggie Magee, 1891 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Little Miss Killarney, 1913 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Little Red Lark, The, undated (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Little Skillet Pot, The, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Little Tommy Murphy, 1900 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Little Town in the Ould County Down, 1920 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Little Widow Dunn, The, 1879 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Live in My Heart and Pay No Rent, 1902 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Londonderry Air, 1928 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Londonderry Air (2), 1935 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Look What My Boy Got in France, 1918 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Love Dreams, 1923 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Love of the Shamrock, The, 1879 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Lovely Katie, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Love's Old Sweet Song, c. 1914 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Low Back'd Car, The, 1846 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Luck O' the Road, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - M
    - Mac O-Macorkity, 1877 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Macnamara's Band, 1917 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Macushla, 1910 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Mademoiselle O'Toole, 1911 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Maggie McGlynn, 1896 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Maggie Murphy's Home, 1890 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Maggie O'Reilly, 1903 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Maggie, Darling, Now Good Bye, 1872 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Maguires, The, 1881 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Major O'Flaherty, 1893 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Mamie Brady's the girl for me, 1899 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Man Know Thyself, c. 1900 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Mar-an-da, 1908 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Márie Ann, 1910 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Martyrs of Ireland, The, 1916 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Mary, 1918 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Mary Ann, 1904 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Mary Ann O'Sann, 1915 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Mary Ellen, 1903 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Mary Kelly's Beau, 1880 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Mary O'Brien, 1921 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Mary Regan, 1919 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Mary Tracy 'How would you like to become a Casey?', 1921 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - McAlheeny's Cake Walk, 1899 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - McCarthy in Picardy, 1918 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - McCormick the Masher, McNeil Chord System, 1879 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - McNulty's Café, 1892 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Me Little Dudeen, 1913 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Meet Me In Rose Time Rosie, 1908 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Meet Me Sweet Kathleen in Honeysuckle Time, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Meet Mister Callaghan, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Meeting of the Waters, The, undated (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Message of a Dying Engineer, The, 1908, 1913 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Michael McGinnity, 1904 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Mick McGilligan's Ball, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Mickey, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Mickey Donohue, 1923 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Mickey O'Neil, 1921 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Micky, Midnight Sons, The, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Mike, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Mike Doolin's Jaunting Car, 1905 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Mike McCarty's Wake, 1894 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Milk Maid of Tyrone, The, 1888 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Minni-Ha-Ha-Donohue, 1908 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Minstrel Boy, The, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Minstrel of Clare, The, Minstrel Show Guide, 1896 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Miss Katy Donahue, 1909 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Miss Killarney, 1910 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Miss Mary, 1905 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Miss Molly O'Moore, 1930 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Miss O'Leary's Irish Fruit Cake, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Mister Dooley, 1902 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Mister Gallagher and Mister Shean, 1922 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Mister Moon and Turn Off the Light, 1910 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Mister Pat O'Hare, 1910 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Mollie Casey, 1897 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Mollie Darling, 1871 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Mollie the Pride of Mayo, 1884 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Mollie Vaughn, 1925 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Molloy, My Boy, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Molly Dear, It's You I'm After, 1915 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Molly Malone, 1909, 1919, 1927 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Molly McGee, 1916 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Molly McGinnity, You're My Affinity, 1907 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Molly Melone, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Molly Me Own, 1916 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Molly O, 1921 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Molly O'Halloran, 1904 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Molly O'Morgan, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Molly on the Shore, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Molly O'Reilly, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Molly O'Rourke, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Molly O'Shaughnessey, 1912 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - 'Mong the Green Irish Hills, 1908 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Moonlight, 1921 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Mother in Ireland, 1922, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Mother Machree, 1910 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Mother Mavourneen, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Mother O'Me, 1917 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Mother O'Mine, 1914 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Mountains o'Mourne, The, undated (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Mr. Doolin' Stop Your Foolin', 1899 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Mr. Mulcahey Esquire, 1885 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Mr. Mulligan and Mr. Garrity, 1925 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Mrs. Delaney of Newport, 1903 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Mrs. O'Harahan, 1905 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - M'self, 1922 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Muldoon, the Solid Man, 1874 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Muldoon's Big Bassoon, 1919 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Mulligan Guard, The, 1873 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Murphy's Head, 1892 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Mush, Mush, Mush, Tural-I-Addy, undated (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Musical Micheal Magan, 1916 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - My Barney Lies Over the Ocean, 1919 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - My Beautiful Irish Maid, 1894 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - My Beautiful Old Land, 1867 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - My Bernadine, 1905 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - My Charming Irish Lady, 1904 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - My Daddy's Auld Dudeen, 1911 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - My Dark Rosaleen, 1897 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - My Dear Irish Mother Who's Waiting For Me, 1920 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - My Dear Little Irish Girl, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - My Dublin Mary, 1910 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - My Fair Kathleen Ashtore, 1918 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - My First Love Was Irish, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - My Galway Rose, 1921 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - My Girl's An Irish Girl, 1947 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - My Heart Is Irish, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - My Heart Is With You Ireland, 1921 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - My Heart Tells Me, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - My Heart was in Old Ireland that Eve, 1900 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - My Heart's in Old Kilkenny, 1914 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - My Heart's in Old Killarney, 1936 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - My Heart's in Tipperary, 1915 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - My Heart's Tonight in Erin, 1914 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - My Home Near Killarney, 1935 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - My Irish American Rose, 1918 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - My Irish Caruso, 1909 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - My Irish Cinderella, 1917 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - My Irish Colleen, 1912 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - My Irish Colleen (2), 1917 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - My Irish Daisy, 1905 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - My Irish Dream Girl, 1914 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - My Irish Fluffy Ruffles, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - My Irish Girl, 1911 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - My Irish Girl (2), 1906 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - My Irish Girlie, 1909 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - My Irish Jaunting Car, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - My Irish Maid, 1905 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - My Irish Maid (2), 1907 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - My Irish Molly O, 1905 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - My Irish Mother, 1939 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - My Irish Paradise, 1929 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - My Irish Prairie Queen, 1909 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - My Irish Rosary, 1923 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - My Irish Rose, 1906 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - My Irish Rosie, 1906 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - My Kathleen, 1915 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - My Kathleen (2), 1947 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - My Kathleen's Gone Over the Sea, 1887 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - My Kilkenny Home, 1920 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - My Killarney Rose, 1911 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - My Killarney Rose (2), 1916 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - My Lagan Love, 1905 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - My Land, 1910 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - My Lass from the Land of the Shamrock, 1906 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - My Little Blarney Stone, 1908 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - My Little China Doll, 1917 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - My Little Cottage Home in Sweet Killarney, 1917 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - My Little Irish Canary, 1904 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - My Mother's Rosary, 1915 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - My Mother's Wedding Ring, 1917 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - My Name Is Kelly, nd, 1919 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - My Name Is Paddy Leary, 1916 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - My Nelly's Blue Eyes, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - My Own Colleen, 1896 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - My Own Dear Irish Queen, 1903 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - My Own Home Town In Ireland, 1915 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - My Pal Flanagan, 1930 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - My Pretty Colleen, 1907 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - My Rose of Erin's Isle, 1916 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - My Rose of Old Kildare, 1912 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - My Rose of Tipperary, 1915 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - My Sweet Colleen, 1909 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - My Sweet Derry Rose, 1913 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - My Sweetheart from Old Donegal, 1916 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - My Sweet Liberty Queen, 1915 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - My Sweet Little Colleen, 1915 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - My Wild Irish Rose, 1899, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - My Wild Irish Rose of Killarney, 1906 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - N
    - Nancy, 1924 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Nancy Clancy, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Nellie Kelly I Love You, 1922 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Never Let Yourself Forget That You Are Irish Too, 1915 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Never Take the Horseshoe from the Door, 1880 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Ninepenny Fidil, The, 1904 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Noel D'Irlande, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - No Irish Need Apply, 1863 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - No One Knew O'Grady, 1898 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - No One Knows, 1913 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Norah-Floradora, undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Nora Kildare, undated (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Nora Machree, undated (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Nora Malone, 1909 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Norah McNamara, 1908 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Norah McShane, undated (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Nora, My Irish Queen, 1911 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Nora, My Irish Rose, 1906 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Nora O'Neal, 1866 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Noreen, 1913 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - O
    - O'Brien, 1910 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - O'Brien Has No Place to Go, 1908 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - O'Brien is Looking For You, 1917 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - O'Brien is tryin' to learn to talk Hawaiian, 1916 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Och, Girls Dear, 1916 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - O Erin! Remember Thy Glorious Past, 1921 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Off to Philadelphia, undated (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Officer Flaherty Whistles a Tune, 1938 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Officer Kelly, 1924 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Oft in the Stilly Night, undated (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Oh Bay of Dublin!, undated (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Oh, Did You Ne'er Hear of the Blarney, 1916 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Oh! Did You Not Hear of Kate Kearney, 1916 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Oh God! Set Old Ireland Free!, 1917 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Oh, He Promises, 1880 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Oh! How He Can Sing An Irish Song, 1914 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Oh! Molly Bawn Why Leave Me Pining, undated (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Oh! Paddy Dear, 1916 (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - Oh! Really O'Reilly!, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - Oh! Steer My Bark to Erin's Isle, undated (Box 30, Folder 41)
    - Oh! The Moment Was Sad, 1916 (Box 30, Folder 42)
    - Old Boreen, The, 1915 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Old Country, The, 1952 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Old Erin, the Home of my Heart, 1878 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Old Erin, the Shamrock and You, 1914 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Old Fashioned Irish Girl, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Old Green Isle, The, 1903 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Old Ireland, 1925 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Old Ireland You're My Darlin', 1865 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Old Ireland's Free and Calling Me, 1922 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Old Irish Sweetheart of Mine, 1933 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - O'Malley's Tango, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - O Mrs. O'Flarity, what did you mean by that, 1892 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - On the Banks of Killarney, 1913-1915 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - On the Green Shores of Erin, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - On the Hoko Moko Isle, 1916 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - On the Road to Dublin Town, 1915 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - On Union Square, 1886 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Once Upon A Time, 1917 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - O'O'O'Brien, 1902 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Open the Door, dear Arrah, for me, 1865 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - O'Rafferty's Hare, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - O'Reagans, The, 1886 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - O'Reilly, 1904 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Ould Plaid Shawl, The, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Ould Plaid Shawl, The (2), 1895 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Over in Erin, 1917 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Over the Hills to Mary, 1915 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Over There, 1917 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - O Would I Were in Ireland, 1912 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - P
    - Paddy, 1906, 1933 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Paddy Carey, undated (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Paddy Carey's Fortune, undated (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Paddy Duffy's Cart, 1881 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Paddy McGinty's Goat, 1917 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - Paddy O'Carroll, undated (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Paddy Shay, 1889 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Paddy's Day, 1905 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Paddy's Jig, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - Paddy-the-next-best-thing, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Paddy Whack, 1907 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Pat Malloy, 1865 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Pat Malloy (2), 1867 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Patricia O'Brien, 1910 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Patsey McKim McCann, 1895 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Patsy, 1906, 1907 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Patsy Dear, 1907 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Pearl O'Rielly, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Peek-A-Boo, undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Peek-A-Boo (2), 1881 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Peggy, 1919 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Peggy (2), 1919 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Peggy Brady, 1903 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Peggy Cline, 1892 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Peggy Gilroy, 1913 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Peggy Malone, 1916 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Peggy McVey, 1918 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Peg O' My Heart, 1913, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Peggy O'Neal, 1903 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Peggy O'Neil, nd, 1921 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Pepita Maguire, 1904 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Phil the Fluter's Ball, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Pick A Little Four Leaf Clover, 1918 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Pictures in the Firelight, 1912 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Pinkerton Detective Moon, 1912 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Pipers of Kilkenny, The, 1937 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Plain Mamie O'Hooley, 1903 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Ploughman, The, 1951 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Policeman McGlue, 1887 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Poor Irish Boy, The, 1854 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Poor Mary Anne O'Shea, 1917 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Pretty Kitty Blue Eyes, 1944 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Pretty Kitty Doyle, 1896 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Pretty Kitty Kelly, 1920 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Pretty Mollie Shannon, 1901 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Pretty Molly Shannon, 1922 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Pride of Tipperary, The, 1925 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Primrose Waltz, 1896 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Princess of My Heart, The, 1917 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Prisoner's Song, The, 1924 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Pull the Cork out of Erin, 1917 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Purity, Honor, and Truth, 1894 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Put On Your Old High Hat, 1912 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - R
    - Rafferty, 1903 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Rafferty's Chime, 1914 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Rafferty's Racin' Mare, 1906 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Remember Boy You're Irish, 1888 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Remember the Poor, 1900 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Reminiscences of Ireland, undated (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Return With the Springtime Acushla Machree, 1915 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Rip Rip Rip, 1901 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Rising of the Moon, The, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - River Shannon Moon, 1923 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Rooney, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Rory O'Moore, undated (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Rory O'Mory and Me, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Rose Maguire, 1896 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Rose O'Day, 1941 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Rose of Kildare, The, 1912 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Rose of Killarney, 1876 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Rose of Tralee, 1933, 1935 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Rose of Washington Square, undated
    - Roses of Erin, The, 1911 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Rose Sweet Rose, 1904 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Rosie Machree, 1927 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Rosie O'Reilly, 1923 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Rosie O'Ryan, 1926 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Roving Kind, The, 1950 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - S
    - Sadie O'Brady, 1924 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Saint Patrick, undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Sally and Irene and Mary, 1921 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Santiago-Flynn, 1908 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Saturday Night in Dublin, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Savourneen Deelish, undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Savoy Irish Medley, The, 1924 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Say! Have You Seen O'Houlihan?, 1890 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Says I to Myself, Says I, 1917 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Scanlan's Rose Song, 1883 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - See Saw and Saw Saw, 1894 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Shadowland, 1914 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Shaeffer's Jig, undated (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Shaeffer's Jig (2), undated (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Shamrock and the Rose, The, 1915 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Shamrock Belles, 1912 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Shamus O'Brien, 1870 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Shannon, The Shamrocks, And You, The, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Shaughraun Quadrilles, The, 1877 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - She Lives in Donegal, 1941 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - She Lives on Munray Hill, 1882 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - She Never Kissed Anything Else Except the Blarney Stone, 1917 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Sheelah, 1907 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Sheelah Magee, 1894 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - She's A Flower from the Fields of Old Ireland, 1909 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - She's Another Sweet Mother Machree, 1927 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - She's the Daughter of Mother Machree, 1915 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - She's the Mother of Peggy O'Neal, 1921 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - She's Waiting in Old Ireland, 1913 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Sho-Heen Sho, 1955 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Shoogy-Shoo, The, 1897 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Silent, O'Moyle! Be the Roar of thy Water, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Silly Boy, The, 1883 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Since Arrah Wanna Married Barney Carney, 1907 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Since I Fell in Love with Mary, 1910 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Since Maggie Dooley Learned the Hooley Hooley, 1916 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Since O'Keefe is On Relief, 1935 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Sing A Good Old Irish Song For Me, 1917 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Sing An Irish Song To-Night, 1914 (Box 35, Folder 12)